[{"answer": "I am feeling good.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Are you primed and ready for the kill?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Is that what it feels like?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I feel like every day since then.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "How many times have you relived that 0.17 of a second?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you have to cut down on all your social activities.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What are you not allowed to do?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Yes, you are.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Are you allowed even in your height of training, are you allowed to have binge eating days?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "I didn't -- I didn't know about that.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "And is it true there's like this group wide sex ban on the entire American team before the Olympics?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Literally, none of you are allowed to do anything like that.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Is it what?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, I'm praying for God.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What are you thinking of?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Mixed emotions.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "How are you going to be feeling?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "ELIX: It's not the same.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Because when you're on the podium, and you won the gold for the relay, are you still thinking this is great, but it's not the same?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, personally, my family.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Personally and professionally?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "She has nails in her family.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Isn't she the one with the phenomenal nails?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Aren't you?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, definitely.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "You think about the commercial benefit to winning the gold?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I do, I have a man.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "ORGAN: Got a man in your life?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "He's done a little running in his time but he's kind of transitioning out of it and just getting ready for the next phase of his life.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "What does he do?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "My mind doesn't function so after the --", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Wedding bells?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I can't even -- I don't know.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Are you allowed to even be thinking about this?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to be in such a good mood.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Are you more or less likely to marry him if you win gold?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Probably would.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "You would do anything, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "It's disappointing, especially for me because when I got into traffic and field, she was everywhere.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "When you think of her story what do you think of it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "It's very hard for me to have sympathy, I don't know.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for her?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "ELIX: Well, of course.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Do you have suspicions about some of your rivals?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Like your body changing.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Wow, that's a tough question.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "When you line up for the 200-meter final, how many people in that race could be cheats?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "It's hard.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "She's very smart, but I mean -- I will tell you.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "How does that work with a dog?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "It is, yes.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "It's going to be a huge moment for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "So proud.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How do you feel about being an American flying the flag for America at such a prestigious event?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Maybe it's time to stand up, beat your chest and show the Chinese who's real boss?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh, I have no plan.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "If you win, what's the plan after that once you've achieved your great aim?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I think it's tough because situations like Marion, you know, she never failed a drug test.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Is that the way to really tackle this?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Well, you'd have to be a very rich man.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "That would -- that would root it out, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I think it's part of it.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "I mean do you have to have that streak of self-confidence?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I'm taking the gold.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I guess, yes.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I see myself as a normal 19-year-old kid.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Is that how you see yourself?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Yes, I guess.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Who just happens to be a gold medal contending power ball?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Growing up in the Bronx, especially as a gymnast, not easy.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "It wasn't masculine enough for them?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I love -- I took gymnastics because it's one of the most challenging sports in the world and that's what I love about it.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Why gymnastics?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I mean, well, look at my parents.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "What are the good parts of you that you think come from being a Bronx guy?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I --", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Did you get into fights as a kid in the Bronx?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Did everybody have to fight if you're a young man growing up in the Bronx?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Knives as well?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "No, thanks god.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Was he stabbed?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "That life is unpredictable and you can't let -- you can't hold on to that.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What did it teach you, the incident?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I would say it takes a lot of willpower and a lot of sacrifice and a lot of self-motivation.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "What does it take to be as good as you are at what you do?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Nineteen.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "What are you, 19?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "It's not.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "This is not a world that you're allowed to do, right?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "I think if I do my absolute best, I think I might have a chance at being on the medal stand, top three in all-around.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "If you perform at your absolute best, what can you achieve in London?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "That would be a dream come true.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "If you win a gold, how is that going to make you feel, a boy from the Bronx winning an Olympic gold medal, standing on that podium, the American National Anthem playing?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Definitely an emotional moment for me and my family.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "It would be an emotional moment for you, huh?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "That's what I'm hearing.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Really, I am?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Are you ready for screaming women chasing you down the street?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "No, never.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "-- shoot up in your face as you stand there?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "A tiny little bit of told you?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Come on, it will be a little bit, won't it?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Maybe a little bit.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "I don't mean vengeful, but more like vindication?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Being an American?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Well, you must have a lot of Polish people on your staff.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "It's like, whoa, Coach K. Why are you such a big deal?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Well, I've been lucky to be at place where their brand helped me right away.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "What does it mean to you to have that reputation?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Well, the very first thing is you don't go with assumptions.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "And what are you going to do to stop it from happening in London, when the whole world assumes you're going to win gold quite easily?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Well, the very first thing is you're honest with them.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "How do you get it to gel and to work, where they have to share that status?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think it is.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Is the American dream still as attainable as it was when you were young?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Intellect does not know race, color, nationality, gender.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "But if they are driven out of an education system that doesn't nurture them, then how can we blame them?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "The main thing is to be truthful, where you're honest with one another.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "What are the values you like to instill in them, human values?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Well, incredible commitment.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "What does it take to be a champion sportsman, not just a winner or a good sportsman, or even necessarily a great sportsman, but a champion over a long period of time?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "In London, looking around Kobe Bryant, Lebron James, Chris Paul, whoever you choose as your starters.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "The first game?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "You keep it simple.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "What do you say to guys like that in that moment?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "I think we don't know when to stop.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "When you see somebody like him, as a sportsman yourself, is the resounding lesson to just know when to stop?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "I'm going to feel OK.", "docId": "120704pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "If you get badly beaten by a young whipper snapper, how are you going to feel?", "qSentId": 816}]